conceptshare.com 2009-04-19

# Privacy Policy - ConceptShare

ConceptShare Inc. ("we") collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site and the quality of our service. It is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

We will transfer information about you if ConceptShare Inc. or ConceptShare™ Web Application is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ConceptShare Inc. will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### INFORMATION GATHERING AND USAGE

When you register for ConceptShare™ Web Application we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address and credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card number.

ConceptShare Inc. uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact and research.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the ConceptShare™ service.

We use cookies to record current session information. In order to protect you against others accidently accessing your account content, you are required to login to your ConceptShare™ Account Site after a certain period of inactivity.

### CLIENT DATA STORAGE

Although ConceptShare Inc. owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the ConceptShare™ application, you retain all rights to your data and we will never sell or share your client data with any third parties, contact your clients directly or use your data for our own business advantage. We will also not utilize your data in our databases to compete with you, market to your clients or advertise to, or contact them for any other means of profit. We respect the privacy of our subscribers and the privacy of their client data.

### DISCLOSURE

ConceptShare Inc. may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

### CHANGES

ConceptShare Inc. may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ConceptShare™ account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to Support at ConceptShare.com, by mail at: ConceptShare Inc., 2041 Long Lake Rd., Sudbury, ON P3E 4M8 Canada, or by phone: 1-800-705-5541 (Outside of North America 705-222-8052).
